Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection, 63573
  - Composer: Frohlich, Heinz Title: Vale carissima Uniform Title: Vale carissima (Fritz Schimpf, Tubingen [printer]), undated; 31142040613211; 66159 (Box 175, Folder 3288)
  - Composer: Frohlich, Heinz Title: Verlorenes Lieb Uniform Title: Verlorenes Lieb (Gust. Sturner, Waiblingen [printer]), undated; 31142040613211; 66158 (Box 175, Folder 3296)
  - Composer: Frohlich, Heinz Title: Weisst du nicht, dass Fruhling ist Uniform Title: Weisst du nicht, dass Fruhling ist (Fritz Schimpf, Tubingen [printer]), undated; 31142040613211; 66157 (Box 175, Folder 3284)
  - Composer: Fromm, E. Title: Begrussungschor Uniform Title: Begrussungschor Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 108a. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613427; 66156 (Box 154, Folder 2384)
  - Composer: Fromm, E. Title: Walzer Uniform Title: Walzer Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 115 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613237; 66155 (Box 173, Folder 3175)
  - Composer: Fucik, Jules (Julius) Title: Marche fantastique Uniform Title: Marche fantastique Publisher information: Prague (Czech Republic): Mojmir Urbanek Plate Number: 131a, undated; 31142040614391; 66154 (Box 17, Folder 201)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Dem Unendlichen Uniform Title: Unendlichen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14323 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040612866; 66153 (Box 101, Folder 1322)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 6464, undated; 31142040613096; 66152 (Box 124, Folder 1805)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.6465, undated; 31142040613385; 66151 (Box 158, Folder 2513)
  - Composer: Fuhrich, Carl Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Uniform Title: Ralf Ringelhaar Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart Plate Number: F.E.C.L.6513, undated; 31142040613385; 66150 (Box 158, Folder 2512)
  - Composer: Gabriel-Marie Title: La Cinquantaine Uniform Title: Cinquantaine Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 10744, undated; 31142040612908; 66149 (Box 105, Folder 1474)
  - Composer: Gabriel-Marie Title: Serenade Badine Uniform Title: Serenade Badine Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3472-9, undated; 31142040614383; 66148 (Box 18, Folder 209)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Comala Uniform Title: Comala Plate Number: 10,863, undated; 31142040613187; 66147 (Box 133, Folder 1890)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Comala Uniform Title: Comala Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 7543, undated; 31142040613187; 66146 (Box 133, Folder 1889)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 11094, undated; 31142040613575; 66145 (Box 139, Folder 1939)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 11109, undated; 31142040613567; 66144 (Box 140, Folder 1962)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 11112, undated; 31142040613567; 66143 (Box 140, Folder 1961)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Die Kreuzfahrer Uniform Title: Kreuzfahrer Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 11293, undated; 31142040613336; 66142 (Box 163, Folder 2720)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter. Ballade Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2075, undated; 31142040613005; 66141 (Box 115, Folder 1634)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2074, undated; 31142040613195; 66140 (Box 134, Folder 1892)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2076, undated; 31142040613195; 66139 (Box 134, Folder 1891)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Uniform Title: Erlkonigs Tochter Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2858, undated; 31142040613195; 66138 (Box 134, Folder 1893)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Uniform Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 9810, undated; 31142040613369; 66137 (Box 160, Folder 2628)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Uniform Title: Fruhlings-Botschaft Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 9811, undated; 31142040613369; 66136 (Box 160, Folder 2627)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Gondelfahrt Uniform Title: Gondelfahrt Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bartholf Senff Plate Number: 78,424, undated; 31142040613393; 66135 (Box 157, Folder 2483)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Holbegian. Suite fur Orchester Uniform Title: Holberg suite, op. 61 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): V. Durdilly, Paris (Breitkopf and Härtel [printer]) Plate Number: 17130/32, undated, undated; 31142040614383; 66134 (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Holbergiana. Suite fur Orchester Uniform Title: Holberg suite, op. 61 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 17130, undated; 31142040614383; 66133 (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 12164, undated; 31142040612973; 66132 (Box 112, Folder 1601)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 12199, undated; 31142040612965; 66131 (Box 111, Folder 1599)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 12223, undated; 31142040612965; 66130 (Box 111, Folder 1600)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Kalanus Uniform Title: Kalanus Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: 12363, undated; 31142040613310; 66129 (Box 165, Folder 2792)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Nachklange von Ossian, op. 1 Uniform Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.181., undated; 31142040614383; 66128 (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Konzert-Ouverture fur Orchester, op. 1 Uniform Title: Nachklange von Ossian. Ouverture. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.193., undated; 31142040614383; 66127 (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Composer: Gade, Niels Wilhelm Title: Reiters Morgenlied Uniform Title: Reiters Morgenlied Plate Number: 1595, undated; 31142040613278; 66126 (Box 169, Folder 2979)
  - Composer: Gageur, Eugen Title: Die Krone im Rhein Uniform Title: Krone im Rhein Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.1742 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613476; 66125 (Box 149, Folder 2154)
  - Composer: Galbraith, J. Lamont Title: Give a Man a Horse He Can Ride Uniform Title: Give a Man a Horse He Can Ride Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: 75760-9, undated; 31142040613344; 66124 (Box 162, Folder 2686)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan, arr. Title: Marietta Uniform Title: Marietta Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 4463 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613302; 66123 (Box 166, Folder 2859)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Frau Einzig Uniform Title: Frau Einzig Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F.E.C.L. 4061 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613385; 66122 (Box 158, Folder 2522)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Uniform Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): F. E. C. Leuckart (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. E. C. L. 3865 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613294; 66121 (Box 167, Folder 2892)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Maiden with the lips so rosy Uniform Title: Madchen mit dem rothen Mundchen Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 4755, undated; 31142040613294; 66120 (Box 167, Folder 2893)
  - Composer: Gall, Jan Title: Maritetta Uniform Title: Marietta Publisher information: New York: Luckhardt and Belder Plate Number: 178, undated; 31142040613245; 66119 (Box 172, Folder 3094)
  - Composer: Gambke, Fritz Title: Das Katzchen Uniform Title: Katzchen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Part.B. 1979., undated; 31142040613476; 66118 (Box 149, Folder 2156)
  - Composer: Gamse, Albert, arr. Title: Havah Nagilah Uniform Title: Havah Nagilah Publisher information: New York: Larrabee Publications, undated; 31142040613211; 66117 (Box 175, Folder 3301)
  - Composer: Gartner, John B. Title: Das Lied vom schlimmen Matrosen Uniform Title: Lied vom schlimmen Matrosen; arr., undated; 31142040612650; 66116 (Box 80, Folder 1028)
  - Composer: Gartner, John B. Title: Matrosenlied Uniform Title: Matrosenlied; arr. Publisher information: New York: Quartet Publishing House, undated; 31142040613294; 66115 (Box 167, Folder 2865)
  - Composer: Gasteiner, Robert Title: Luarin Uniform Title: Luarin Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6473 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613310; 66114 (Box 165, Folder 2804)
  - Composer: Gay, Noel Title: There's Something about a Soldier Uniform Title: Soldiers of the King. There's Something about a Soldier Publisher information: New York: Mills Music Inc. Music Publishers, undated; 31142040613377; 66113 (Box 159, Folder 2555)
  - Composer: Geehl, Henry Ernest Title: Dawn. A Prelude Uniform Title: Dawn. A Prelude; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Gould and Bolttler Plate Number: G and B. 1656., undated; 31142040614383; 66112 (Box 18, Folder 210)
  - Composer: Geibel, Adam Title: Annie Laurie Uniform Title: Annie Laurie Publisher information: Boston: Oliver Ditson Company Plate Number: F. A. N. and Co. 3817.6, undated; 31142040613492; 66111 (Box 147, Folder 2098)
  - Composer: Genaro, Pat, and Sunny Skylar Title: You're Breaking My Heart Uniform Title: You're Breaking My Heart Publisher information: New York: Algonquin Music Inc., undated; 31142040613385; 66110 (Box 158, Folder 2533)
  - Composer: Genee, Richard Title: Italienischer Salat Uniform Title: Italienischer Salat Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 2541, undated; 31142040613344; 66109 (Box 162, Folder 2692)
  - Composer: Genee, Richard Title: Reise um die Erde in 12 Minuten Uniform Title: Reise um die Erder in 12 Minuten Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Friedrich Schreiber (A. Eckel, Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: F. S.23876. Engraver: Eberle and Schipek, undated; 31142040613096; 66108 (Box 124, Folder 1797)
  - Composer: Gericke, Wilhelm Title: O welt du bist so wunderschon! Uniform Title: O welt du bist so wunderschon! Plate Number: L. and S. 131, undated; 31142040613286; 66107 (Box 168, Folder 2906)
  - Composer: German folksong Title: Christmas Night Uniform Title: Weihnacht; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 12636, undated; 31142040613484; 66106 (Box 148, Folder 2130)
  - Composer: German, Edward, Sir Title: Gipsy Suite. Four Characteristic Dances Uniform Title: Gipsy Suite. Four Characteristic Dances Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Novello and Company Plate Number: 9933, undated; 31142040614383; 66105 (Box 18, Folder 211)
  - Composer: German, Edward, Sir Title: Suite Uniform Title: Suite; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22917, undated; 31142040614375; 66104 (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Das Grab im Busento Uniform Title: Grab im Busento Plate Number: F. L. 138, undated; 31142040613492; 66103 (Box 147, Folder 2090)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Odin's Meeresritt Uniform Title: Odin's Meeresritt Publisher information: New York: Edward Schuberth and Co., undated; 31142040612973; 66102 (Box 112, Folder 1608)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Uniform Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 499, undated; 31142040613583; 66101 (Box 138, Folder 1930)
  - Composer: Gernsheim, Friedrich Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Uniform Title: Salamis. Siegesgesang der Griechen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): J. Rieter-Biedermann Plate Number: 503, undated; 31142040613583; 66100 (Box 138, Folder 1929)
  - Composer: Gersbach, Jos. Title: Voglein, Blumlein und Bachlein Uniform Title: Voglein, Blumlein und Bachlein, undated; 31142040613005; 66099 (Box 115, Folder 1643)
  - Composer: Gevaert, François-Auguste Title: The Emigrants Uniform Title: Auswanderer Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 3602, undated; 31142040613419; 66098 (Box 155, Folder 2409)
  - Composer: Giese, Theodor Title: Blümlein vergiss mein nicht (Flowret Forget-me-not). Gavotte Uniform Title: Blümlein vergiss mein nicht Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 15948, undated; 31142040612908; 66097 (Box 105, Folder 1471)
  - Composer: Gilbert, Jean Title: All for the Girlies Uniform Title: Autoliebchen. Das Haben die Madchen so gerne, undated; 31142040613518; 66096 (Box 145, Folder 2025)
  - Composer: Gillet, E. Title: Bonheur Perdu (Lost Happiness) Uniform Title: Bonheur Perdu; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3627-18, undated; 31142040614383; 66095 (Box 18, Folder 208)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Au Moulin (In der Muhle) Uniform Title: Au Moulin; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2314-27, undated; 31142040612817; 66094 (Box 96, Folder 1201)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Babillage (Plauderei) Uniform Title: Babillage; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2314-27, undated; 31142040612817; 66093 (Box 96, Folder 1200)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Douce Caresse (Zartliche Umarmung) Uniform Title: Douce caresse Publisher information: Nice (France): Paul Decourcelle (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: P. D. 251, undated; 31142040612833; 66092 (Box 98, Folder 1238)
  - Composer: Gillet, Ernest Title: Loin du bal. Waltz Movement Uniform Title: Loin du bal; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1894-11, undated; 31142040612890; 66091 (Box 104, Folder 1404)
  - Composer: Ginkel, Henry, and Al Havranek, arr. Title: Alter Sang, Neuer Klang Uniform Title: Alter Snag, Neuer Klang Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer, undated; 31142040612940; 66090 (Box 109, Folder 1557)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Carl Simon, Musikverlag Plate Number: C. S. 1946, undated; 31142040613344; 66089 (Box 162, Folder 2671)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Bremen (Germany): A. E. Fischer Plate Number: 2537, undated; 31142040613344; 66088 (Box 162, Folder 2672)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E. E. 823 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613344; 66087 (Box 162, Folder 2669)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ernst Eulenberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: E. E. 824 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613344; 66086 (Box 162, Folder 2670)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug and Co. Plate Number: G. H. 3045., undated; 31142040613344; 66085 (Box 162, Folder 2673)
  - Composer: Girschner, C. F. J. Title: Hute dich! Uniform Title: Hute dich! Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre Plate Number: 7591, undated; 31142040613344; 66084 (Box 162, Folder 2674)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Marche, op. 76 Uniform Title: Marche, op. 76 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 2372, undated; 31142040614375; 66083 (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Novelette, op. 22, no. 2 Uniform Title: Novelette, op. 22, no. 2; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 22370-41, undated; 31142040614375; 66082 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Valse de Concert pour Grand Orchestre, op. 47 Uniform Title: Valse de Concert pour Grand Orchestre, op. 47 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 918 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614375; 66081 (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Composer: Glazunov, Aleksandr Konstantinovich Title: Valse de Concert, op. 47 Uniform Title: Valse de Concert, op. 47 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaieff Plate Number: 919, undated; 31142040614375; 66080 (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Composer: Glessmer, Felix Title: Schon bluh'n die Heckenrosen Uniform Title: Schon bluh'n die Heckenrosen, undated; 31142040613245; 66079 (Box 172, Folder 3086)
  - Composer: Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich Title: Kamarinskaia Uniform Title: Kamarinskaia Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): M. P. Belaiff Plate Number: 3011 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040614375; 66078 (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Composer: Glinka, Mikhail Ivanovich Title: Rouslane et Ludmila. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruslan I Liudmila. Ouverture Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 15899., undated; 31142040614375; 66077 (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Composer: Gluck, Christoph Willibald Title: Iphigenia in Aulis. Ouverture Uniform Title: Iphigenie en Aulide. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf and Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.182., undated; 31142040614367; 66076 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Composer: Gluck, Christoph Willibald Title: Iphigenia in Aulis. Ouverture Uniform Title: Iphigenie en Aulide. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: C. 39382., undated; 31142040614367; 66075 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Composer: Glueck, F. Title: Untreue Uniform Title: Untreue Plate Number: 7162, undated; 31142040613237; 66074 (Box 173, Folder 3151)
  - Composer: Glueck, F. Title: Untreue Uniform Title: Untreue Plate Number: 7163, undated; 31142040613120; 66073 (Box 127, Folder 1840)
  - Composer: Glueck, Fr., arr. Title: Klage Uniform Title: Klage; arr. Publisher information: New York: F. A. Rockar Plate Number: F. A. R. 701-4, undated; 31142040613120; 66072 (Box 127, Folder 1839)
  - Composer: Gobbaerts, Jean-Louis Title: Les Puritains. Opera de Bellini. Fantaisie Brillante Uniform Title: Puritains. Fantaisie brillante Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: S. F. 2751, undated; 31142040612890; 66071 (Box 104, Folder 1419)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Louis Paul Title: Six Duets for 2 violins with piano accompaniment Uniform Title: Duettini, 2 violins andamp; piano, op. 18 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 6905, undated; 31142040612841; 66070 (Box 99, Folder 1276)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: 2me. Mazurk Uniform Title: Mazurka, piano, no. 2 Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 4759, undated; 31142040612908; 66069 (Box 105, Folder 1439)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Adagio Pathetique, op. 128, no. 3 Uniform Title: Adagio Pathetique, op. 128, no. 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22201, undated; 31142040614367; 66068 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Berceuse from Jocelyn Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Berceuse; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 4689-36, undated; 31142040614367; 66067 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Canzonetta, op. 35, no. 3 Uniform Title: Canzonetta, op. 35, no. 3; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 23003, undated; 31142040614375; 66066 (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Deauxieme Mazurk, op. 54 Uniform Title: Deauxieme Mazurk, op. 54 Publisher information: Boston: White-Smith Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 6942-8, undated; 31142040612858; 66065 (Box 100, Folder 1284)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Act 2. Prelude Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Act 2. Prelude Publisher information: Paris (France) (E. Dupre, Paris [printer]) Plate Number: A.C. 7124, undated; 31142040614367; 66064 (Box 20, Folder 231)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Act 2 Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Act 2 Publisher information: Paris (France) Plate Number: A.C. 7909, undated; 31142040614367; 66063 (Box 20, Folder 230)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Jocelyn. Gavotte Uniform Title: Jocelyn. Gavotte Publisher information: Paris (France): Choudens Fils Plate Number: A.C. 8119, undated; 66062 (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Composer: Godard, Benjamin Title: Scenes Poetiques Uniform Title: Scenes Poetiques; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22232, undated; 31142040614375; 66061 (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Composer: Goebel, Friedel Title: Du bist verkehrt verheirat Uniform Title: Du bist verkehrt verheirat Publisher information: Wuppertal-Langerfeld (Germany): Hermann Goebel, undated; 31142040613518; 66060 (Box 145, Folder 2054)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7718, undated; 31142040613427; 66059 (Box 154, Folder 2390)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7719 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613161; 66058 (Box 131, Folder 1882)
  - Composer: Goetz, Hermann Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Uniform Title: Es liegt so abendstill der See Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): N. Simrock (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 7721 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated; 31142040613161; 66057 (Box 131, Folder 1883)